[{"answer": "I'm doing great, I just met Bob Newhart at the back.", "docId": "130919pmt", "aSentId": 11, "question": "Billy Ray Cyrus, probably the famous father on planet earth right now, Billy Ray how are you?", "qSentId": 10}, {"answer": "Well, I'm telling you, starstruck.", "docId": "130919pmt", "aSentId": 13, "question": "Are you speaking with excitement about this?", "qSentId": 12}, {"answer": "I'm a singer, songwriter, you know, first and foremost, you know.", "docId": "130919pmt", "aSentId": 28, "question": "So what is your view of this huge Miley controversy?", "qSentId": 27}, {"answer": "I knew that she wanted to do something really special and something that everybody was going to be talking about.", "docId": "130919pmt", "aSentId": 39, "question": "Did you know what she was going to do at the awards?", "qSentId": 38}, {"answer": "Well that's what music is supposed to do is make you feel, you know, that's what music is supposed to do.", "docId": "130919pmt", "aSentId": 51, "question": "What do you say to those people who perhaps were huge fans of Hannah Montana and feel uncomfortable about the directions she's taking?", "qSentId": 50}, {"answer": "She has been so busy, like I mean every single night she's in the studio.", "docId": "130919pmt", "aSentId": 80, "question": "Does she have any regrets about it or is she loving every second of the mayhem this caused?", "qSentId": 79}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "130919pmt", "aSentId": 98, "question": "As a dad?", "qSentId": 97}, {"answer": "She's never been arrested you know.", "docId": "130919pmt", "aSentId": 114, "question": "I mean, have I missed it all or she's pretty good as that?", "qSentId": 113}, {"answer": "Well, I'm on the council, you know.", "docId": "130919pmt", "aSentId": 124, "question": "What is your response to those like that council and like people that have subscribed to it who have got serious concerns about what Miley did?", "qSentId": 123}, {"answer": "They sure didn't (ph) too.", "docId": "130919pmt", "aSentId": 129, "question": "Well they get very angry about things like Miley did?", "qSentId": 128}, {"answer": "Yes, you can.", "docId": "130919pmt", "aSentId": 134, "question": "You know the old saying, right, I mean you don't want me to say it do you?", "qSentId": 133}, {"answer": "It does seem like a whole new level and yes, she has been very famous but she has reason to a whole new level and it's -- I thought I'd seen it all until these last couple of weeks and the whole thing just kind of went to a whole new level.", "docId": "130919pmt", "aSentId": 145, "question": "Do you think she'd be the biggest pop star in the world there, I mean she's been famous but this is a like a whole new level, isn't it?", "qSentId": 144}, {"answer": "Every single day.", "docId": "130919pmt", "aSentId": 191, "question": "Did you think about your friend often?", "qSentId": 190}, {"answer": "I did.", "docId": "130919pmt", "aSentId": 196, "question": "Did you question your faith at all in that?", "qSentId": 195}, {"answer": "Exactly.", "docId": "130919pmt", "aSentId": 208, "question": "Because if you don't have that, you just have endless acrimony right?", "qSentId": 207}, {"answer": "\"Hope is Just Ahead\".", "docId": "130919pmt", "aSentId": 231, "question": "What will you be singing for us?", "qSentId": 230}, {"answer": "Yes, I'm delighted with it.", "docId": "130919pmt", "aSentId": 249, "question": "Bill Donohue, let me ask you first of all, you're a pretty well- known hard line conservative on these matters, are you happy with the direction the Pope wants to take you?", "qSentId": 248}, {"answer": "Well I -- Now I -- would I endorse it.", "docId": "130919pmt", "aSentId": 296, "question": "Would you endorse every word of what he said about?", "qSentId": 295}, {"answer": "I tell you, people in all denominations, they are wondering -- they're wondering why this Pope is saying what he's saying, and they do see a sense of reform taking place.", "docId": "130919pmt", "aSentId": 361, "question": "On abortion?", "qSentId": 360}, {"answer": "I'm not coming back.", "docId": "130919pmt", "aSentId": 377, "question": "Is that what you're saying father?", "qSentId": 376}, {"answer": "It's heavy.", "docId": "130919pmt", "aSentId": 402, "question": "Is it big and heavy as it looks?", "qSentId": 401}, {"answer": "Actually, he's a genius.", "docId": "130919pmt", "aSentId": 411, "question": "Is he dangerous?", "qSentId": 410}, {"answer": "I think I thanked Mr. Ed.", "docId": "130919pmt", "aSentId": 428, "question": "Were there any names on the original acceptance speech that actually survived to the final moment when you want one?", "qSentId": 427}, {"answer": "Well, and first of all it's your peers, you know, its your peers who are saying --and I kind of, you know, I kind of said, well I'm just never going to get one, because when you come from a stand up comedy world it's like let's just --that's Bobby and Bob and that's Bill Cosby and me and Bill Cosby and that's Jerry Seinfeld, me and Jerry Seinfeld.", "docId": "130919pmt", "aSentId": 442, "question": "How did it make you feel mostly?", "qSentId": 441}, {"answer": "All right, Bob.", "docId": "130919pmt", "aSentId": 459, "question": "But don't you want to hear about it?", "qSentId": 458}, {"answer": "That I was an inn keeper in this craziest little town in Vermont.", "docId": "130919pmt", "aSentId": 461, "question": "What is it?", "qSentId": 460}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130919pmt", "aSentId": 469, "question": "Your wife had that idea, right, for the finale scene?", "qSentId": 468}, {"answer": "That's what I said.", "docId": "130919pmt", "aSentId": 499, "question": "You're afraid of flying?", "qSentId": 498}, {"answer": "I think, as you said, a breath of fresh air.", "docId": "130919pmt", "aSentId": 530, "question": "Are you a fan?", "qSentId": 529}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "130919pmt", "aSentId": 535, "question": "Oh, really?", "qSentId": 534}, {"answer": "EWHART: Well, I like -- at first, it's not the modern crop anymore.", "docId": "130919pmt", "aSentId": 556, "question": "So, who do you find funny of the modern crop of comedians when you see them?", "qSentId": 555}, {"answer": "Well, I can put my finger on the mirror.", "docId": "130919pmt", "aSentId": 575, "question": "Is there anybody under 90 you could put your finger on that makes you laugh other than Don Rickles?", "qSentId": 574}, {"answer": "I'm not -- I know Ricky.", "docId": "130919pmt", "aSentId": 577, "question": "Do you like Ricky Gervais and Russell Brand and that style of British talent?", "qSentId": 576}, {"answer": "Once I get the translation.", "docId": "130919pmt", "aSentId": 580, "question": "What about Ricky Gervais, when you see him (inaudible) people at the Emmy's, is that you find him funny?", "qSentId": 579}]